The Coffin Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Coffin Family Documents, 1
  - Folder 9: Tabor Bently Inventory and Estate, Folder 9; 1
    - Conditions of the sale by auction of a parcel of land belonging to the estate of Tabor Bently (deceased) to the highest bidder, Beriah Austin, drafted by Robert Coffin, executor - March 2nd, 1839, 145 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Folder 10: Miscellany, Folder 10; 1
    - Bill and receipt of funds from Wheeler Gilbert by Robert Coffin, 146 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Note of sale and receipt of payment to Roswell Warner - January 7th, 1831, 147 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Receipt of funds by Roswell Warner - January 8th, 1831, 148 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Personal note to Robert Coffin from Samuel Thorn - August 11th, 1830, 149 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The ear mark of Robert Coffin is a swallow fork in the left ear and a slit in the far side of the right ear - July 1st, 1813: Cleared by Town Clerk Vimah Woolley, 150 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Promise of payment by John Donald to Peter Worden for value received - April 30th, 1828, 151 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Promise of payment (fulfilled) by Robert Coffin to Isaac Thorn paid in two installments - April 29th 1828 and May 3rd, 1828, 152 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Receipt of funds from Robert Coffin by Patience Holmes for interest on a bond against Martin Robinson - July 13th, 1833, 153 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Folder 11: Research Materials and Secondary Sources, Folder 11; 1
    - Coffin Family Biographical Sketch from History of Dutchess County, New York by James H. Smith, 154 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1820 Federal Census for Dutchess County, New York (copy), 155 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Background information on Tabor Bently, 156 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Marriage certificate of Enoch Haight and Lucena Bristol from The American History and Genealogy Project (copy), 157 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Poughkeepsie Journal article “Escaped Slaves Find Support and Refuge on Way to Freedom”, 158 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Cemetery records: Hicksite Friends’ Burial Ground, Clinton Corners, Dutchess, NY courtesy New York Local History Network, 159 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Cemetery records: Friends’ Ground, Mechanic, Dutchess, NY courtesy New York Local History Network, 160 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Quaker Removals from Nine Partners courtesy New York Local History Network, 161 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Heads of Families: Oblong and Nine Partners Circularly, Dutchess, NY courtesy New York Local History Network, 162 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Email concerning the collection’s provenance and the relationship between Robert Coffin and Tabor Bently, 163 (Box 1, Folder 11)